

DYLAN MCADAM Product Designer

I am a product designer with seven years of creative experience and a research background who specializes in conversion optimization and internal tooling solutions. In my free time, I am outdoors, globetrotting, or learning a new skill.

United States

+1 207-613-5776

dylanpmcadam@gmail.com

dylanpmcadam.com

EXPERIENCE

Senior Product Designer

The Washington Post

- Conceptualized and tested product page user experience improvements that resulted in a \$2.74M year-one subscription increase
- Planned and launched a marketing A/B testing tool that increased experimentation speed by 90%—saving \$11K per campaign

September 2021 - Present / Remote

Product Designer

Govini

- Led strategic design system initiatives to implement design tokens, create a system documentation site, and standardize 400+ components
- Collaborated on cross-functional teams to design innovative features for B2G
 SaaS platform: a simplified data search, a chart editor, and a new homepage

July 2020 - August 2021 / Remote

Visual & Conversation Designer

Inmar Intelligence

- Shipped ecommerce chatbots for major brands such as Pepsi, Lyft, Budweiser, Family Dollar, Snickers, and KeVita
- Designed conversation scripts and marketing assets for a Super Bowl chatbot that engaged over 16,000 users

January 2020 - April 2020 / Seattle, WA

SKILLS

User Research	Animation	Sketch	Design Systems
A/B Testing	Branding	Figma	Copywriting
Prototyping	Adobe Suite	InVision	HTML, CSS, JS

EDUCATION

Macalester College

Bachelor of Arts, GPA: 3.5

Major: Biology, Minors: Geography & Philosophy

2011 - 2015 / St. Paul, MN